Guide to the United Brewery Workers Local 266 Records, 1947-1979 AIS.1984.10
ULS Archives & Special Collections
United Brewery Workers Local 266 Records
1947-1979
ULS Archives & Special Collections
International Union of United Brewery, Flour, Cereal, Soft Drink and Distillery Workers of America. Local 266 (Leechburg, Pa.)
AIS.1984.10
6.25 Linear Feet (5 boxes)
International Union of United Brewery, Flour, Cereal, Soft Drink and Distillery Workers of America Local 266 represented workers in Leechburg, Pa. This collection contains contract negotiation and meeting minutes of Local 266.
Related Material
United Brewery Workers Pennsylvania Council Records, 1938-1983, AIS.1984.12, Archives & Special Collections, University of Pittsburgh
United Brewery Workers, Local 267 Records, 1936-1959, AIS.1984.11, Archives & Special Collections, University of Pittsburgh
Access Restrictions
No restrictions.
Acquisition Information
Gift of Robert Carpen in 1984.
History
International Union of United Brewery, Flour, Cereal, Soft Drink and Distillery Workers of America Local 266 represented workers in Leechburg, Pa. The union began as United Distillery Workers of North America Local 3 before it changed to United Distillery Workers Local Industrial Union No. 3 and Distillery Workers Local 266 before finally settling on this name. The union represented workers at Joseph S. Finch & Company in Logansport, Pennsylvania, for a time, but mostly consisted of employees at Schenley Distillery, which closed in 1984.
Previous Citation
United Brewery Workers, Local 266 Records, 1947-1979, AIS.1984.10, Archives Service Center, University of Pittsburgh
Scope and Content Notes
This collection contains contract negotiation and meeting minutes of Local 266. Also included are correspondence, employment records, and notices from the company to workers.
Labor; Leechburg (Pa.); Brewery workers -- Labor unions -- Pennsylvania -- Leechburg; Schenley Distillery; International Union of United Brewery, Flour, Cereal, Soft Drink and Distillery Workers of America. Local 266 (Leechburg, Pa.)
- Agreement, 1947 (Box 1, Folder 1)
- Negotiation Minutes, 1947 (Box 1, Folder 2-3)
- Agreement, 1948 (Box 1, Folder 4)
- Contract between Crotty and United Distillery Workers Local 3, 1948 (Box 1, Folder 5-6)
- Negotiation Minutes, 1948 (Box 1, Folder 7-8)
- Shop Committee Minutes, 1948 (Box 1, Folder 9)
- Agreement, 1949 (Box 1, Folder 10)
- Contract with Crotty, 1949 (Box 1, Folder 11)
- Negotiation Minutes, 1949 (Box 1, Folder 12-13)
- Shop Committee Minutes, 1949 (Box 1, Folder 14-18)
- Contract Negotiation Minutes, 1950 (Box 1, Folder 19)
- Bureau of Labor, Statistics, 1953-1954 (Box 1, Folder 20)
- Personnel Notices, 1953-1954 (Box 1, Folder 21)
- Documents Sent to the National Labor Relations Board, 1949-1954 (Box 1, Folder 22-27)
- Grievance Reports, 1953-1954 (Box 1, Folder 28)
- Communications, 1953-1954 (Box 1, Folder 29)
- Employment Action Records, 1954 (Box 1, Folder 30)
- Ballots, Grievance Representatives, 1953-1954 (Box 1, Folder 31-32)
- Grievance Reports, 1955-1956 (Box 1, Folder 33)
- Communication from Joseph S. Finch & Company, 1955-1956 (Box 2, Folder 1)
- Communications, 1956 (Box 2, Folder 2)
- Personnel Notices, 1955-1956 (Box 2, Folder 3-5)
- Contract with Joseph S. Finch & Company, 1958, 1961 (Box 2, Folder 6-7)
- Agreement with Schenley, 1962 (Box 2, Folder 8)
- Contract with Joseph S. Finch & Company, 1966 (Box 2, Folder 9)
- Communications, 1967 (Box 2, Folder 10)
- Letters of Notice, 1967 (Box 2, Folder 11)
- Communications, 1968 (Box 2, Folder 12-14)
- Layoffs, 1968 (Box 2, Folder 15-16)
- Leaves of Absence, 1968 (Box 2, Folder 17)
- Personnel Notices, 1968 (Box 2, Folder 18)
- Recalls at Joseph S. Finch & Company, 1968 (Box 2, Folder 19-20)
- Communications, 1969-1970 (Box 2, Folder 21-23)
- Employment Action Record, 1970 (Box 2, Folder 24-25)
- Layoffs, 1970 (Box 2, Folder 26-27)
- Leaves, 1970 (Box 2, Folder 28)
- Letters of Notice, 1970 (Box 2, Folder 29)
- Personnel Notices, 1970 (Box 2, Folder 30)
- Recalls, 1970 (Box 2, Folder 31-32)
- Communications, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 33)
- Employment Action Records, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 34-35)
- Communications, 1972 (Box 3, Folder 1)
- Communications from the International Union, 1972 (Box 3, Folder 2)
- Contract Termination at Schenley, 1972 (Box 3, Folder 3)
- Employment Action Records, 1972 (Box 3, Folder 4)
- Layoffs, 1972 (Box 3, Folder 5)
- Personnel Notices, 1972 (Box 3, Folder 6)
- Recalls, 1972 (Box 3, Folder 7)
- Communications, 1973 (Box 3, Folder 8)
- Communications from the International Union, 1973 (Box 3, Folder 9)
- Employment Action Records, 1973 (Box 3, Folder 10-11)
- Layoffs, 1973 (Box 3, Folder 12)
- Leaves of Absence, 1972-1973 (Box 3, Folder 13)
- Personnel Notices, 1973 (Box 3, Folder 14-15)
- Recalls, 1973 (Box 3, Folder 16)
- Communications, 1974 (Box 3, Folder 17)
- Employment Action Records, 1974 (Box 3, Folder 18-19)
- Personnel Notices, 1974 (Box 3, Folder 20-21)
- Leaves of Absence, 1974-1975 (Box 3, Folder 22)
- Communications, 1975 (Box 3, Folder 23)
- Employment Action Records, 1975 (Box 3, Folder 24-25)
- Personnel Notices, 1975 (Box 3, Folder 26-27)
- Communications, 1976 (Box 3, Folder 28)
- Employment Action Records, 1976 (Box 3, Folder 29)
- Employment Action Records, 1976 (Box 4, Folder 1)
- Layoffs and Recalls, 1976 (Box 4, Folder 2)
- Leaves of Absence, 1976 (Box 4, Folder 3)
- Personnel Notices, 1976 (Box 4, Folder 4-6)
- Communications, 1977 (Box 4, Folder 7)
- Employment Action Records, 1977 (Box 4, Folder 8-9)
- Layoffs and Recalls, 1977 (Box 4, Folder 10)
- Leaves of Absence, 1977 (Box 4, Folder 11)
- Personnel Notices, 1977 (Box 4, Folder 12-14)
- Reprimands, 1977 (Box 4, Folder 15)
- Election, Grievance Representatives, 1978 (Box 4, Folder 16-17)
- Employment Action Records, 1978 (Box 4, Folder 18-19)
- Layoffs and Recalls, 1978 (Box 4, Folder 20)
- Leaves of Absence, 1978 (Box 4, Folder 21)
- Personnel Notices, 1978 (Box 4, Folder 22)
- Personnel Notices, 1978 (Box 5, Folder 1-2)
- Reprimands, 1978 (Box 5, Folder 3)
- Unions Notices, 1978 (Box 5, Folder 4)
- Employment Action Records, 1979 (Box 5, Folder 5-6)
- Layoffs and Recalls, 1978 (Box 5, Folder 7)
- Personnel Notices, 1979 (Box 5, Folder 8-10)
- Reprimands, 1979 (Box 5, Folder 11)
- Sick Leave, 1979 (Box 5, Folder 12)
- Union Notices, 1979 (Box 5, Folder 13)
- Contract Negotiation Minutes, 1979 (Box 5, Folder 14-17)
- Contract between Schenley and Distillery Workers Local 1, 1947 (Box 5, Folder 18)
- Contract between Bernhein and Distillery Workers Local 90, 1949 (Box 5, Folder 19)
- Contract between New England Distilling and Distillery Workers Local 6, 1949 (Box 5, Folder 20)
- Contract between Pellbeford Distillery and Distillery Workers Local 91, 1948 (Box 5, Folder 21)
- Miscellaneous (Box 5, Folder 22)
- Charter for Local 266: International Union of Brewery, Flour, Cereal, Soft Drink and Distillery Workers (Map-case 3, Drawer 11)